Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Wealth, fame, power.
Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Gold Roger, the King of the pirates, attained this
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
and everything else the world had to offer.
Quality Control
FishyBusyness
Gab
Galaxy 9000
Gol D. Rocks
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
StanMan
Westfal
Zenef
FishyBusyness
Gab
Galaxy 9000
Gol D. Rocks
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
StanMan
Westfal
Zenef
And his dying words drove countless souls to the seas.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Timing
Gab
Villager
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
Subtitle Editing
Pollychan
Zenef
I left everything I gathered together in one place.
Raws
Neo-Raws
Translation
Funimation
Nikki
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes
and dreams.
Together we will find everything that we're looking
for.
One Piece!
The compass left behind, it'll only slow us down.
Your Heart will be your guide, raise the sails
and take the helm.
That legendary place that the end of the map reveals
Is only legendary until someone proves it real.
Through it all, through all the troubled times,
through the heartache and through the pain, know that
I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along all your hopes
and dreams.
Together we will find everything that we're looking
for.
There's always room for you If you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise We are
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
The Silent Man
Brutton woman!
How dare you try to make a fool of the great Captain Usopp!
Insulting me for having the blood of a pirate?
Please, you don't have to do this, Usopp!
Klahadore?
Klahadore, are you there?
Hello, Klahadore?
No!
Mary!
What's going on?
What happened to you?
Please wake up!
Mary!
Please don't die!
Oh, thank goodness.
You're still alive.
I was worried.
Mary!
You have to tell me who did this to you!
Klawhador.
That's who.
He attacked me.
He's a. . .
He's a pirate.
He's never been anything else.
How could that be?
He got close to you just so he could steal your Fortune.
That's all he ever wanted.
And what Usopp spoke about yesterday was the truth.
That's right.
And that's what is most tragic.
When he learned the truth, he tried his hardest to
get us to hear him out.
But we we're all too shallow-minded, too confident in
the closed-off world we've lived in for
so long to listen to a single word.
Quick!
Run, Kaya!
They're going to kill you!
I promise this will all make sense tomorrow!
In our blind protection of the villain in our midst,
we drove away the one brave lad whose desperate
resolve he enacted for the sake and safety of every
person of this village, including you and I.
Someone help!
Mary needs help!
No, miss.
It's of no use.
The entire staff is on leave.
No one has been here since yesterday.
What?
Then I just. . .
I'll find. . .
You cannot let yourself get flustered, miss.
We know the attack has yet to begin.
So be calm, and think clearly about what it is you
Have to do next.
Because if Klawhador is the thief we understand him
to be, and his goal is your fortune and your mansion,
then by all means, let him have it.
None of this is worth sacrificing your life over.
Yes.
It's a cruel truth, but you are the only one who can
stop Klawhador now, Kaya.
Can you do it?
I know this is not your
burden, but still, I must ask.
Yes, I understand, and I will do it.
This isn't a situation I can run away from.
I know what consequences I face.
I will find Klawhador and I will finish this.
What?
You saw Klawhador heading to the shore?
Yeah, and he had this weird, scary look on his face.
Carrot, would you wake up?
Come on, it's way too early for this.
This is no time for laziness.
Horrible things could be happening right now.
I still think the pirates are going to attack soon.
I know our Captain said that was a lie,
but I think he was the one that was lying.
Yeah, you're probably right.
It was weird.
He seemed off yesterday.
The Captain wasn't his usual self.
It's Kaya.
She's all right.
Looks like something's got her really bothered.
Yeah, walking around outside
by yourself doesn't seem right.
Something's going on.
Something really weird.
Come forth, Meowban!
Siam
Ship Guard
Black Cat Pirates
Siam
Ship Guard
Black Cat Pirates
Siam
Ship Guard
Black Cat Pirates
Yes, Captain?
Did you call for us?
Butchie
Ship Guard
Black Cat Pirates
Butchie
Ship Guard
Black Cat Pirates
Butchie
Ship Guard
Black Cat Pirates
Well, did you?
Siam!
And Butchie!
Together we are the Meowban brothers!
At your service.
Butchie, Siam, we absolutely must get up this hill,
but as you can plainly see, our path is blocked.
If you would be so kind as to remove this obstacle immediately.
No way!
We couldn't do that.
He looks too strong.
Right, Butchie?
Oh, yeah, he's strong.
Way stronger than us. Huh?
Besides, we just guard the ship, not fight people.
He's got a point.
We're really not the guys
you want to send into battle.
So, they're a couple of pansies.
I guess they're not the trump card after all.
Siam, just do it already.
What?
He's not me.
And hurry!
Okay, I'll go.
Just stop yelling.
The guy's crying like a baby.
What are they doing down there?
Of all people, why force that guy into a fight?
I'm going to tear you up with these claws!
You just wait and see!
I'm a vicious killing machine and I'm coming for you!
You bad people!
You come any closer and I'll cut you in half!
I'm not joking!
I'll do it!
Not likely.
Preston
Too bad.
It seems you fell for my little ruse.
I'm impressed you blocked me, considering what a
brilliant performance I gave.
Don't let the teeny bit of skill you have cause you
to underestimate Siam of the Meowban brothers.
Are you missing something?
Not that I would know anything about it.
There it is.
Cat burglar.
Give me my swords back.
Your swords?
But you already have a sword.
How greedy can you be?
Say goodbye, swords.
Goodbye.
Now I feel lighter.
You should take care with other people's things!
You really have to be faster,
because I'm agile as a cat.
Butchie, you're up.
Get in here.
Sedentia!
Damn, Butchie.
He got away from you.
Now he's right there, and I hold him tight this time.
Careful, he's strong.
Stronger than I thought he'd be, even without all his blades.
This is getting worse by the second.
If tubby there would have landed on me, I'd have been
pounded into the dust.
We'll get him for sure this time.
You got that right.
One-sword technique's not my forte, fellas,
but what the hell?
Let's go, Butchie!
Right, Siam, let's do it!
This isn't good.
They got him on the defensive.
What are you doing, Usopp?
There's no way that Zoro can gain any ground
if he's too busy blocking their attacks.
I'm going to help him.
Take this!
Let's go!
This is our chance!
You're supposed to shoot at the bad guys, you idiot!
But I did!
It was. . .
It was like he moved in front of my shot on purpose.
But why would he do that?
Dumbass!
Don't help me!
You want to die?
It's just a thought, but maybe it's the two of us who
just got saved.
If you had actually hit one of those guys, they would
Have come after us instead.
And we wouldn't have had a chance of holding up
against that.
What a guy.
All this time he was worried about us.
If I just had one more sword, I could take these guys.
I'm going to get the swords.
If I can get them back to Zoro, there'll be no way he
can lose.
Let me get the swords.
Don't push yourself.
You can barely even stand up on your own.
Nami!
What do you need swords for?
No!
I'm sorry!
I can explain all of this!
The night has long since passed.
So why is it that you seem to have made no progress
on the plan?
Captain!
Kuro! No!
He'll kill us all!
It's all over.
What the hell is going on?
To think that these brats have held you back.
How the Black Cat Pirates have fallen.
What have you got to say for yourself?
Djongo!
But, , well, I. . . You said. . .
Sorry, sir, but you said letting the kid go wouldn't
cause any problems.
I did say that.
What's your point?
He's an idiot.
I knew no one would listen to his warnings
and he would come stumbling back to take a stand
against us.
But the one thing I hadn't taken account for was your
inexcusable weakness!
We're not weak.
It's just that. . .
Who are you to call us weak?
What would you say, Captain Kuro?
You used to be quite the killer.
But face it, Kuro, it's been three years,
and we haven't exactly been living the good life
waiting on a rich girl hand and foot.
Yeah, that's right.
For three long years, we've been out sinking pirate ships
and massacring villages.
Very good.
Finished?
No!
You've done nothing this whole time!
We've been killing!
You butler, there's no way you can beat the Meowban brothers!
Don't!
Butchie!
Siam!
Stop!
You are not Captain anymore!
So sorry, but we have to kill you!
What?
He's behind them.
How the hell did he. . .
I'm one of those crazy weapons.
Who are you going to kill?
He snuck up right behind us! Huh?
He's gone!
Pussyfoot maneuver.
You know, you're right.
I do feel a bit sluggish after all these years.
He's handling them like babies.
And those two nearly defeated Zoro.
With his pussyfoot maneuver, Captain Kuro could shred
everyone on this beach
before we drew our next breath.
We wouldn't even see it coming.
There is no escape from a killing machine like him.
I knew he hadn't grown soft
when I saw that old habit of his.
That strange way of lifting his glasses
so that he won't cut his face.
It's like he never stopped wearing those cat claws.
They're almost a part of his body.
Of course he hasn't forgotten how to fight.
You're very lucky.
I'm feeling somewhat merciful.
Maybe these years on dry land have made me soft.
I'll give you five minutes.
If you can't deal with the situation here in five
minutes, then I'll kill every last one of you.
Now have I made myself clear?
Oh, yes.
Yes, of course, that's perfectly clear.
Thank you for being so forgiving.
All we have to do is take care of this one guy.
That's all.
Five minutes will be more than enough time for them.
We nearly had him a few minutes ago.
We won't need one minute to finish him this time.
We're counting on you.
Kill him!
Kill him dead!
Zoro!
What the?
Hey, easy there.
You can't just kick them.
Those are my swords.
How about a thanks?
Yeah.
I appreciate it.
You idiot.
It won't matter how many swords you have.
And now you'll die holding three of them.
Tiger.
You still don't get it.
The clock is ticking.
Carrying three swords won't help you at all.
Unless you know three swords style.
Oh no.
This is bad.
He took down the Meowban brothers with one attack!
Don't worry.
I can promise you everything will be taken care of in
less than five minutes.
Three.
Three minutes left.
I'll slaughter him!
Please, Captain!
I can do it!
Hypnotize me!
Just do it, Captain!
He's still alive.
You do sloppy work.
So he is.
I guess all that blubber protected his vitals.
Butchie!
Kill him!
What, really?
You back for more?
This guy knows business.
He was trouble when he was half this size.
Then Django had to flip his psycho switch.
Now's my chance.
I got to wake that lazy jerk up while I still can!
What is that girl up to?
Something tricky, I'm sure.
Everyone else is busy fighting for their lives
and he's just sleeping!
Get up, you bum!
Nami!
Look out!
It was nice knowing you.
Dodge it!
Quick!
Hey, stop it!
I thought it was just a hypnotic charm,
but it's also his weapon.
Nami, you cannot just go around stepping on people's
eyes!
How is that twerp still alive?
That's either the best timing or the worst timing in
the world.
I can't tell.
Luffy?
Luffy!
Crap!
That guy's back in the battle!
No!
This is terrible!
Five minutes will never be enough time.
That hurts, you jerk!
Why'd you do that?
Hey, Sleeping Beauty, that wasn't me!
It wasn't me.
You okay?
Nami, did you get hurt?
Let me see it.
Oh, it's nothing.
I'm fine.
I've done everything I can for now.
The rest is up to you.
Look, we have to win.
We can't afford to lose this fight.
Do you understand?
Okay, go.
Win this and protect my treasure.
Yeah, yeah, the treasure.
I get it.
One minute and counting.
Kuro can't be serious!
We can't possibly finish them in one minute!
Come on, guys!
Stop messing around and end this already!
Butchie, quickly!
There's no more time to waste!
Kill that three-sword bastard!
I'll take care of the freaky, bendable Kid!
I'm coming for you, Straw Hat!
Hey, wait!
Why is that shady Butler here?
It's that Kid.
Didn't he die falling off a cliff?
Nice trick.
Don't ever sneak up on me.
Unless you want to die.
Kaya!
Usopp
Kaya, what are you doing here?
Ussop, I'm so sorry.
I don't know how you'll ever forgive me.
I just couldn't believe it.
That Kalahador is a scheming, murdering pirate.
Never mind that.
Why are you here?
Kaya, your life is in danger.
I told you to run somewhere safe.
I won't.
You're still here fighting.
I won't run.
You fought for me after I treated you so badly.
Look at you.
You're barely alive, but you're still so brave.
I just. . .
This is no place for a lady.
Madam, please leave.
Please, stop.
Don't do this.
Stop!
Stop this right now!
Klahadore!
I know what you're up to.
Mary already told me about everything.
What's the girl from the mansion doing down here?
The whole reason that we're here is to murder that
little rich girl.
If she's here, then we don't have to go to the village.
All we got to do is kill her, right?
Klahadore, please.
If you want my Fortune, you can have it.
Take it all and leave this village right now.
I'm begging you.
I will gladly accept your Fortune, Miss Kaya.
Thank you.
But I want more.
You see, simply acquiring wealth isn't enough.
More than anything else.
What I want is peace.
You want peace?
Yes, just peace.
Peace of mind.
It's simple, really.
I have spent the last three years earning the trust
of the entire village.
And to be honest, I find this new sense of peace
and tranquility quite comforting.
When my plan comes to fruition, I will live with this
sublime peace of mind.
Yes.
The glorious comfort of a peaceful life will be mine
for forever and ever.
In short, these pirates are coming.
And you will leave your Fortune to me and die.
Miss Kaya, these things will happen.
No, you can't.
You just can't be.
Run away, Kaya!
There's no use talking to him!
Please, get out of here!
You're not Klahador.
No, you're not!
Kaya. . .
Leave here right now!
Never come back!
Yes, I see.
You're all grown up now.
So much has happened in the last three years.
Miss Kaya. . .
Don't you remember the things we went through?
We spent so much time together.
Even before your dear sweet parents passed away.
You we're more than my master.
You we're my best friend.
So much time.
So many memories.
Together we suffered, and together we rejoiced.
Like family.
Klahador ...
I took you on shopping trips to the city.
I looked after you so diligently when you we're ill.
And we used to talk for hours and hours.
Kaeya, listen to me.
I was devoted to you.
For so long.
For so very long.
I endured it.
I quietly suffered so that today I could end your
life and take everything that I deserve.
I, who was once the feared and respected Captain Kuro
had to bow and humble myself before some
snot-nosed little girl.
It went against every fiber of my being.
Damn you!
Can you understand the depth of these daily insults?
Can you understand the rage created by those
transgressions against my pride?
Thank you for reminding me.
Usopp, I owe you for hitting me.
Let's get even.
Oh, no!
Usopp!
If I recall, you hit me as hard as you could, right?
Huh?
If he hates getting hit that much, he's about to have
a really bad day!