Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Wealth, fame, power.
Video Editing
Feeso
Galaxy 9000
Gold Roger, the king of the pirates, attained this
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
and everything else the world had to offer.
Quality Control
Gab
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Westfal
Zenef
Gab
Galaxy 9000
Grug
Mr. Luffy
Pepperjack
Westfal
Zenef
And his dying words drove countless souls to the
seas.
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Timing
Gab
Lance
Villager
Gab
Lance
Villager
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
Subtitle Editing
Gordingus
Griff
Lil T
Polly
Gordingus
Griff
Lil T
Polly
I left everything I gathered together in one place.
Raws
Neo-Raws
Translation
Funimation
PamkinPinguin
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and
bring along all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything that we're looking
for.
One Piece!
The compass left behind It'll only slow us down Your
heart will be your guide Raise the sails and take the
helm That legendary place That the end of the map
reveals Is only legendary until someone proves it
real.
Through it all, through all the troubled times,
through the heartache and through the pain, know that
I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and
bring along all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything that we're looking
for.
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Captain Kuro
Don't call it murder, Django.
I don't like the sound of it.
Oh, right.
Accident.
It's an accident that you planned.
Uh, what are those guys talking about?
Just be quiet.
Maybe if we listen a little closer, we can find out.
We can't simply kill her.
It is critical to our plan that Miss Kaya perishes in
an unfortunate accident.
So don't screw that up.
So basically, on your signal, the men and I stormed
the village and managed to accidentally kill the
little rich girl.
Then you get her inheritance and
we all get paid, right?
You moron!
Your ignorance is astounding!
We're not related,
so how could I inherit anything from her?
You'll work very hard to.
No, Django, I won't.
Now listen to me.
This is the most important part.
Before you kill her,
you'll use your hypnosis to make Kaia write her will.
And it will say I leave my entire fortune to my
butler, Klawhador.
Then and only then will I have undisputed control of
her enormous fortune.
And no one will suspect a thing.
I have spent three long years gaining the trust of
everyone around me so that it would be unsurprising
for her to leave the entirety of her inheritance to
me.
Three years as a butler for this, huh?
You sure had us scared back then, Captain Kuro.
Three years ago, you suddenly said you were giving up
life as a pirate.
In no time at all,
you set up someone to be your double.
Then you let the world see Captain Kuro get executed.
Only now do I understand that was just the beginning
of this plan.
You are the man of a thousand plans.
Never call me that again.
I abandoned that name years ago.
I now wish to obtain my wealth without attracting the
attention of the government.
In other words, I'm a pacifist.
The pacifist you are?
Murdering an entire family
doesn't exactly qualify as peaceful.
Hold on.
I haven't murdered an entire family.
The father's death wasn't planned.
Whatever you say, it makes no difference to me.
If it's all the same to you,
hurry up and give the word.
The crew is getting bored.
We've been waiting in the
waters near here for over a week.
And the men are growing more anxious by the minute.
This is horrible.
This is really horrible.
What are they talking about?
Is it bad guy stuff?
What?
Weren't you listening to any of that?
Those guys aren't just bad, they're evil.
Captain Kuro is known to be the most devious,
scheming pirate around.
And though he's known for his smarts,
he's legendary for his brutality.
Word had it that the Marines caught and
executed him three years ago.
But Captain Kuro is alive and
well, posing as Klawhador the butler.
And he's had his diabolical sights set on Kaya's
fortune for the last three years.
First they'll attack the village,
then they'll kill Kaya!
This is bad!
This is seriously bad!
Hey, get down!
They'll see you!
Hey, bad guys!
You better stay away from that girl!
Who are you?
You idiot, they've spotted you.
Come on, hurry up and
hide before they decide you need a long, slow death.
Well, now,
if it isn't Usopp, the mischievous town liar.
Oh, no, I'm spotted, too.
Did you hear anything?
Uh, no, nothing at all.
I don't know what you mean.
We didn't hear a peep.
We just got here,
so we didn't hear anything about anything.
We heard it all.
Shut up.
Well, if you say so.
Pay attention, boys!
And watch this ring closely.
Hmm?
Okay.
Don't you get it?
It's some kind of weapon!
We gotta run!
By the count of Django, you will be in a deep sleep.
Are you ready?
One... Run for cover!
Two...
He's going to kill us!
Django!
Huh?
Django, you idiot!
I see you're still falling asleep on the job!
Hey, be careful!
You're going to fall!
He had to go and fall off a cliff, didn't he?
A pity, really.
I didn't mean to kill him.
But there's no way he could have survived.
This can't be happening!
They killed him?
He's really dead!
What about the other one?
Shall I take care of him?
There's no need.
Everything he could say would sound like lies.
Django, tomorrow at daybreak
the men are to attack the village.
Rough up the villagers some and
tear up their homes a little for good measure.
And above all,
make sure Miss Kaya's death looks accidental.
Tomorrow?
Just accept it, Usopp.
There is nothing you can say or
do to warn the villagers of this impending tragedy.
Are you sure about that one?
Of course I am.
My plans are flawless.
I can't believe this!
This is terrible!
I gotta do something!
Everyone in the village I grew up with is in danger!
And Kaya's going to be killed!
Who are you?
I'm Usopp, brave warrior of the sea.
I heard you've been a little down lately,
so I thought I'd tell you a story to cheer you up.
You would do well to mind your own business.
Please leave or
I'll call someone who will make you leave.
And then?
What happened after that?
I fought, of course.
Noooooooo!
Captain!
Hold on.
I thought Luffy was supposed to be with him.
Captain!
Hey, where's Luffy?
Is he still at the shore?
Wow, he looked really upset.
But why?
Still mad at the butler?
Who knows?
No, that wasn't just a mad face.
That look was different.
It was a tragic face of sheer desperation.
Hey, why don't you guys show us the way to get down
to that shore?
This smells like an adventure to me.
Yeah, something happened at the shore.
I think this calls for the Usopp Pirates.
Enough already.
How do we get to this place?
Terrible news.
Pirates!
Pirates are coming!
Everybody run!
We don't stand a chance!
Run!
Tomorrow morning they're going to attack the village!
We gotta get out of here!
What are you doing?
Run!
All right, Usopp.
Enough is enough.
We can't take it anymore.
We're putting a stop to this here and now.
It's for your own good.
No!
It's not like that!
It's the truth this time, I promise!
Stop it!
We all know that you're nothing but a liar.
It would do you some good to follow Klawhador's
example of hard work and honesty.
Everything he could say would sound like lies.
Oh no!
This is exactly what Klawhador is counting on!
He ignored me because
he knew no one would believe me!
Are these to your liking, miss?
Custom made to your exact specifications.
It was quite a trip to get them.
They're just perfect.
Thank you so much for
traveling so far to get them for me.
They're a gift, aren't they?
Yes.
As of tomorrow, it will be exactly three years to the
day since Klawhador arrived here.
He's always taken such good care of me.
He'll be delighted to receive such a lovely gift.
I hope so.
Please hear me out, everyone!
Our lives depend on it!
Listen!
Pirates are going to attack
the village in the morning!
If we believed every story you ever told us, we would
have run screaming from the
village hundreds of times already.
Please believe me!
We don't have time!
I'm not lying this time, I swear!
Don't you get it?
They'll murder you all!
You'll be lucky if we don't murder you!
I'm not lying!
Get him!
Don't let him escape!
After three long years of absence,
I made the call for my men, and you came.
Your loyalty will be richly rewarded.
I intend on being more than generous when
I divide the take.
At dawn tomorrow,
destroy the village to your heart's content.
If the pirates are going to attack the village,
then they're going to kill Kaya?
Yep, that's what they said.
No question about it.
So, what made you think
it'd be a good time for a nap?
That's the thing.
I don't remember going to sleep or
getting down here at all.
This proves it.
Klawhador is a bad guy.
Usopp saw right through him.
I bet he's on his way to warn the villagers so
they'll have time to run away.
Well, that's perfect.
Those stupid pirates won't hurt anyone because the
town will be abandoned by the time they get there.
Yeah, that's right.
We'd better run away too if we want to live.
All right, let's pack our
treasure and run like the wind.
Oh, no.
What's up?
We need to stock up before the meat shop guy leaves.
Come on, that's not really the issue at hand here.
Usopp.
Oh, good.
I was worried you wouldn't come back.
Quick!
Run, Kaya!
They're going to kill you!
Huh?
Someone's going to kill me?
He's tricked the entire village!
Klawhador's really a deadly pirate captain!
Is this a story?
Well, I don't like this one.
This isn't one of my stories!
It's the truth!
I heard it with my own ears!
Klawhador is a pirate captain who weaseled his way into
your family's home so he could steal your fortune!
He's pretended to be your butler for three years so
he could kill you and inherit your money!
What are you talking about, Usopp?
His crew is going to raid the village at dawn,
and in the process, you're going to get killed!
Klawhador's a very bad man!
Your life is in danger!
You have to escape!
I did treat you harshly earlier,
and I understand that you're hurt.
But lying like this, it's not like you.
Kaya, please.
I'm telling you the truth.
I loved them.
Every one.
All those lies you told me.
They brought joy to my heart,
but this is just vengeful poison.
Kaya, please, listen to me.
I'm not just trying to get back at Klawhador.
Why would you do that?
It's wrong.
Kaya, I...
Miss Kaya, is everything okay up here?
Let's get out of here, right now!
Unhand her immediately, you villain!
Please trust me, Kaya.
You gotta get out of this village
before that butler gets back.
Stop it!
C'mon
I promise this'll all make sense tomorrow,
but right now we need to go!
Kaya, please, please, trust me.
Leave Miss Kai alone, you maniac!
Don't let that lunatic get away!
He broke in and tried to
kidnap the lady of the house!
Why?
Why won't anyone believe me?
There, there, ma'am.
Everything's going to be fine.
Captain!
Hey, how's it going, guys?
Hey, Captain!
Wait, you're alive again?
Alive?
Yeah, and I had a pretty good nap.
He was sleeping the whole time.
Captain, we heard all about
those pirates and their evil plan.
We better hurry and warn the people in the village so
they have time to get away.
Warn the people?
Stop it!
We all know you're nothing but a liar.
Well, obviously I'm lying like usual.
That butler made me so mad with what he said.
I thought I'd get him back and
say that he was a pirate.
Oh, I get it.
You put the Straw Hat guy up to it, too.
Where are you going?
Honestly, you've really disappointed me.
Yeah.
Even though that butler guy is a jerk, I thought you
were better than lying to hurt someone and I admired
you for being such a kind-hearted person.
And to think, we respected you this entire time.
Let's go home.
Yeah, it's supper time anyways.
So, how come you lied to them?
Because all I do is lie.
There's no way anybody was
going to believe what I had to say.
Why should they?
Because what you were
telling them was the honest truth.
They are coming,
and they're going to level this whole town.
Yeah, but what am I supposed to do?
They'll think I'm lying if I try to warn them.
Everyone in the village thinks that tomorrow's just
going to be another normal day.
They think I'm lying and
that's all they need to think.
I'm going to stop those pirates
at the beach tomorrow myself.
This is all my fault for being such a liar.
I don't care anymore if they drive me away with
brooms or shoot me in the arm.
This is my village.
It's my home and I love everyone in it.
I have to protect them.
You're a hell of a good guy, sending your cronies
away and going into battle alone.
Just so you know,
I have dibs on all the pirate treasure, you got it?
So you want a little help or what?
You guys?
You're going to help me fight all these pirates?
I don't get it.
Well, you said there's a
whole bunch of bad guys, right?
And you look scared out of your mind.
For your information, I have nerves of steel.
I'm perfectly okay with tons of bad guys.
After all, you're looking at the legendary Captain Usopp,
brave warrior of the high seas.
Dammit!
All right, fine, I'm scared.
Why shouldn't I be?
They're Captain Kuro's men.
These guys mean business.
I don't need pity.
If you guys are sticking around because
you pity me, just leave.
I don't need you laughing at me.
We're not laughing at you.
We're helping because you are honorable.
You really think we'd risk our lives out of pity?
You guys!